Guide to the WVBR records, 1946-2000s.
WVBR records, 1946-2000s.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
WVBR records, 1946-2000s.
35-9-1739
WVBR (Radio Station: Cornell University)
6.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Memorabilia, Photographs, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes reports; letter; station log (1948-1951); minutes of the Cornell Radio Guild, Inc. (1971); Board minutes (1968); published Program Guides (1959-1965); and other materials pertaining to Cornell radio station WVBR.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes reports; letter; station log (1948-1951); minutes of the Cornell Radio Guild, Inc. (1971); Board minutes (1968); published Program Guides (1959-1965); and other materials pertaining to Cornell radio station WVBR and its shows, including Bound For Glory with Phil Shapiro.
SUBJECTS
Names:
WVBR (Radio Station: Cornell University); Cornell Radio Guild.; WVBR (Radio Station: Cornell University)
Subjects:
Radio stations--New York (State)--Ithaca.; College radio stations.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
See also collection #37-7-m.1055 for audio and transcript of the 1952 student raid of WVBR; Robert A. Mayers WVBR - Live Audio, #35-9-3768; and Ted Osborn, WVBR Records, #35-9-3512. Also Bound for Glory records, #35-9-4277.
CONTAINER LIST
- CRG Archives, Manuel, and Bylaws (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Share of Radio Audience States and John Henrehan, 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Various Department Reports, 1968-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Various Department Reports (2), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Various Department Reports (3), 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Various Department Reports (4), 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1966-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- B.O.D. Minutes, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Executive Committee Minutes, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Guild Minutes, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Memos, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Promotional Literature (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Program logs, 1940s-1960s (Box 2)
- Construction Proposal for Antenna Tower; Engineering Report; Tech Training Manuel; FCC License Renewal; Play List, 1958; 1979; 1972; 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Original FM License FCC Application, June 1958 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Application to Move Auxiliary Transmitter, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Application to Put New Transmitter on Hungerford Hill, July 1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Application to Change Broadcast Equipment, July 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Application to Make Changes to Broadcast Station, July 1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Application to Change Transmitter, Dec. 1965 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Notice of Changing Address, August 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Antenna Tower, HAAT Info, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- MSI Composite Limiter, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- FCC Application for Renewal, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- FCC Papers, Construction Permit, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Proofs, 10/18/1964 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- FCC-Form Letters and Mass Mailings (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Newspaper Clippings, NY Grants Broadcast Announcement, Recruitment Posters, 1962; 1970s (Box 3, Folder 15)
- History, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Promotions Summer '83, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Old Public Files, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Missing Link Stuff (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Beatles Song Record (Blank) (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Island Getaway, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- License Renewal, 1998; 2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Lake Placid Getaway, Nov/Dec 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous, 1980s; 1999 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- VP Reports, 1984-1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Spring Training Posters--Moved to 2-12 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- FCC Procedure Manuel, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Application for Construction Permit, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Antenna Schematics for AM Carrier Current, Original 1949; Copied 1983 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Tapetronics Tape Cartridge Technical Manuel (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Tapetronics Technical Manuel-Current Manuel (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Tapetronics Technical Manuel RP Series, May 26, 1078 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Compressor, Amplifier LIterature (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Equipment Catelog, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Instructions for Voltmeter, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Instructions for FM Exciter/Transmitter, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Transmitter Logs (1), 1965-1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Transmitter Logs (2), 1965-1973 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Sketch of Table (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 42)
- System Bloclv/Conn (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Mute Switching (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Mic, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Information on Equipoment "Out of Service" (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Data Sheets (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Bauer Relay Schematics, October 1979 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- A Clean Audio Installation Guide by Allen H. Burdick (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Status Display (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Millet Creations (Box 3, Folder 51)
- FCC Materials, 1984-1991 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Key Telephone System Layout, Diagrams, GSP's, 1970-2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- AC Power-Carport, Garage Stairs, Downstairs, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Comb Lock, 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Maintenance Logs, 12/14/1968-12/17/1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Maintenance Logs (2), 11/26/1974-11/6/1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Maintenance Logs (3), 01/15/1983-04/03/1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Com Arts 318 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Notice of Proposed COnstruction of ALteration, February 25, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Loose Papers--Some materials moved to 2-11 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- HVAC Project Engineering Permits, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Antennas, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 11)
- ELCOM Requested Literature, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Transmission Surge Eliminator Info, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Bird RF Power Management Catalog, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Stereo Gen Hardware (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Portable Radio Equipment (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Stereo Amplifier Manuel (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Equpment Order, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Transmission Lines Manuel (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Untitled, Misc--Some materials moved to 2-10 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Arent Fox FCC Actions, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Cassette Machines Manuels, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Tape Head Specifications and Manuel, 1960s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Tape Transport Schematic,. Optical Remote Control, Magnetometers (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Recording Tape, Cartridge Tape, NAB, 1960s-1970s (Box 4, Folder 25)
- NBC Hotline Code and Pulse Receiver, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Patch Bay Assignment Sheets (Blank) (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Free Response Forms (Blank) (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Multi Conductor Block Sheets #75-100 (Blank) (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Multi Conductor Block Sheets #51-74 (Blank) (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Multi Conductor Block Sheets #24-50 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Multi Conductor Block Sheets #1-24 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Pair Assignment Sheets #51-74 (Blank) (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Pair Assignment Sheets #75-100 (Blank) (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Pair Assignment Sheets #25-50 (Blank) (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Pair Assignment Sheets #1-24 (Blank) (Box 4, Folder 36)
- FCC Public Notice on Translator, February 1985 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Tapetronics (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Record and Monitor Selectors, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Microphone and Accessories, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Miking Techniques, 1948; 1968 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- "The Illustrated Guide to Loudspeaker Healthcare" (Box 4, Folder 42)
- WVBR Clock Driver Schematics (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Phase Reversal Correction Files, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- FM Antenna Maintenance Instructions, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Circuit Diagram of "Sock Hop" Board (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Proposal for WVBR to Join Empire Radio Network (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Packing Invoice to WVBR General Manager Warren Kurtzmann--Some materials moved to 2-8, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Geotechnical Investigation Proposed Radio Tower, December 1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Long-Range Planning Committee Reports, August 1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Bound for Glory/Speciality Show Event Planning (Box 5, Folder 8)
- NY Telephone Access Billing/Technical Charqacteristics of Telco Program Lines, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Bell System Technical Reference, August 1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Report on Replacing Various Station Components (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Scientific Atlanta Product Brochure and Order Form, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- WVBR Technical Wizards Manuel, Fall 1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Scientific Atlanta: Satellite Selection Information, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- News Control and News Work (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Ampex Wiring (Remotes), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Engineering Schematics Drawn on Back of Cornell Dining Menu and Equipment Notes--Some materials moved to 2-9, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Patch Bay Rewiring (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Diagrams for Boards (Box 5, Folder 19)
- E.B.S. Tape (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Drafting Materials (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Letter from Vet School Dean Regarding Snyder Hill Antenna Location, September 1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Information on Emerging Power Generators (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Impedance or Admittance Coordinates (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Report and Assessment of Studio's Vacuum Tubes, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Pettycom-Investigation of a Duplex Comm. System--Some materials moved to 2-7, March 1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- EBS Report and Instructions, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Proof of Performance Measurements, 1965-1983 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Letter to Keith Olbermann Regarding FCC and Arnet, Fox Correspondence, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- FCC Correspondence: Non-Applications (Box 5, Folder 30)
- FCC Applications, Reports, Etc.--Some materials moved to 2-6, 1957-1969 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Station License (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Memorandum from Robert Russell on Growing Media Marketplace in Ithaca, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Robert Russell, Chief Engineer Statement, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Tech Study Guide, Fall 1979 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Reports on Condition of Technical Engineering Dept, Transmitters and Associated Equipment Design of Audio Mixer Bridges, 1963-1984 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous--Some materials moved to 2-5 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Proposed WVBR Transmitter on Bundy Road--Some materials moved to 2-4, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Engineering Study on Bundy Transmitter--Some materials moved to 2-3 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Audio Satellite Distribution NBC; CBS Services--Some materials moved to 2-2, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Scientific-Atlanta Digital Audio Terminal Manual "On Loan" from WHCU (DAT-32, partial instructions) (Box 5, Folder 41)
- WVBR-FM Christmas Cards (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Correspondences with Other STudent Radio Stations RE: FM Signal Construction, 1950s (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Announcements and Correspondences RE: WVBR's Initial Transition to FM, 1956-1959 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 4)
- FCC Violations (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Individual Student Operator Permit Cards--Some materials moved to 2-17, 1977-1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Print Advertisements and Promotions, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Awards and Thank-yous from Various Civic Leaders/Non-Profits/Charities, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Letters to Station Management (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs Quarterly Listing Information (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Programming Memos, Letters--Some materials moved to 2-14, 2-15, 2-16, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- WVBR Advertisement Rate Card, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Issues Relating to Roof Repairs at 227 Linden Ave. (Box 6, Folder 13)
- A.M. Field Str.--Some materials moved to 2-13 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Engineering Schematics and Thoughts on Training, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- FM-64 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- License Renewal Applications, 1972, 1975, 1978, 1981, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Letter to Charlie Mayer Discussing Engineering Status of Station, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Correspondence With Dan Fairbanks on Signal Strength, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- FCC Application, September 1967 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- FCC Public File Compliance Info, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- FCC Provisional Applications (Box 6, Folder 22)
- WVBR Corporate Policy Notebook, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- General Managers Notebook (1), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- General Managers Notebook (2), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- General Manager's Notebook Volume Two (1), 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- General Manager's Notebook Volume Two (2), 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Scripts from Willard Straight Hall Takeover, April 19, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Scripts from Willard Straight Hall Takeover, April 20, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Scripts from Willard Straight Hall Takeover, April 21, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Scripts from Willard Straight Hall Takeover, April 22, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- WVBR Photographs: March on Washington, Up the Junction, Ken Dryden, 1968 Elections, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Sample Letterheads from Before and AFter the FM Revolution of 1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Program Director Steve Marx's Year-End Report, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Steve Marx's Com Arts 521 Paper on Integrating Blacks into the WVBR Staff, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Steve Marx's "Case Study" of WVBR for ILR Course, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Steve Marx's ILR 423 Paper on Staff Training at WVBR, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Floorplans for Ill-Fated Expansion of WSH STudios into Neighboring Craft Shop Space (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Monthly Department Reports (Box 7, Folder 14)
- News Formats and Manuel, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- WVBR Jingles, Bandwagon, Program Schedule and Addresses (Box 7, Folder 16)
- 1969 FCC License Renewal Application (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Cornell Daily Sun Clips, 1966; 1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Serious/Humorous WVBR Glossary of Terms, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Early 1970s meeting minutes, floor plans of Linden Ave, finances, budgets, releases, reports of the general manager, treasurer, radio engineer, audience listener reports. (Box 7, Folder 20)
- 2 WVBR Sweatshirts, one created by Bill Dugatkin, 1966; 1968 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Promotional Posters (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Phase and Polarity in Electrical Wiring--From 5-2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Radial-Site Charts--From 5-39 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Maps--From 5-38 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Letters--From 5-37 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Newspaper Clippings from "Legal Notaries etc."--From 5-31 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Letters--From 5-26 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Proposal to expand and renovate news and sports department facilities--From 5-5 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Capacitors--From 5-17 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Western Electric Telco Recorder Couplers--From 4-20 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Custom Air Boards (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Spring Training Ads--From 3-27 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Diagrams--From 6-14 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Newspaper Clipping from "History of WBR or WVBR"--From 6-11 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Ithaca Journal Clipping--From 6-11 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Format Changes 1983--From 6-11 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- FCC Application--From 6-6 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Program guides, 1959-1962 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Program guides, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Items removed from binder photo and clipping book (Box 15, Folder 3-11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1940s (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper advertisement clippings, 1950s (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Misc. items, Cornell Radio Guild clippings, letter to station about signal, station position employment advertisements (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, includes shots from Willard Straight Hall, 1950s-1970s (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of Linden Avenue studio purchase and renovation, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of station equipment (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of a picnic broadcast event, includes pie tossing, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of people involved with the station. also includes a photo of the Dutch Kitchen, Fred's Record Shop, and a photo inscribed to WVBR by President Deane Waldo Malott of Dwight Eisenhower giving his lecture at Barton Hall in May of 1963, 1960s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Tompkins Weekly article celebrating 50 years of Bound for Glory, August 22, 2018 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Items collected by James H Schoonmaker (Box 15)
  - The Know-it-alls Guide to WVBR; Assorted Guidelines on running a radio station; Internal correspondence, including a letter about possibly covering Summer Jam at Watkins Glen from Sol Taishoff, editor-in-chief of Broadcasting magazine; WVBR-AM (Carrier Current) Sheet; Cornell Countryman report on the WVBR; Newspaper Clippings on WVBR; WVBR Advertisements and Schedules; Photographs., 1971-1973, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Black Affairs Department, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Radio Guild: Constitution, Bylaws, Proposals, Reports, 19701-974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - News clippings on Professor Rose K. Goldstein, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - News clippings on Bettina Gregory, 1974, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Letters commenting on the show "Moment of Sanity", 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Commercial Schedules; Logging Instructions; Rate Cards; Standard Rate and Data Services Sheets; Audience and Media Information, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - News clipping on WTKO, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - News Clipping on new WVBR Headquarters at 227 Linden Avenue; Bids for 227 Linden Avenue Build-out, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - USB Drive HD-32 Electronic Scans of Box 15, Folders 13-20 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Audio / Visual material (Box 9-14)
  - Beethoven, Sym # 2, 2nd Movement, Borodin String Quartet, 1967; tr8341 (Box 9)
  - Burnt Weeny & Times Are Changin’, tr8342 (Box 9)
  - British Biscuit, Emerson, Lake, & Palmer, 12/18/1977; tr8343 (Box 9)
  - Pyramid & Beds, tr8344 (Box 9)
  - SFX Editing, Safe Driving PSA’s, Teen Beat, Bud Splices, Spring 1968; tr8345 (Box 9)
  - Sampler & Shifting Whispering Sounds, tr8346 (Box 9)
  - Queen, Tie Your Mother Down, Live Ithaca, Lou Reed, 1977; tr8347 (Box 9)
  - Same One Tape, Never Erase, Steve Miller - Book of Prezhons, tr8348 (Box 9)
  - Spartagus Side 1 & 2, One Night In Paris Side 1 & 2, Tape 3, tr8349 (Box 9)
  - Training MTG Blooper, No Box, Sept, 1983; tr8350 (Box 9)
  - Netfeed, RKO Coct, Promo for TRYA giveaway, Production Bloopers, 1984; tr8351 (Box 9)
  - Apollo 13 Past Splashdown, April, 1970; tr8352 (Box 9)
  - Queen 1st Album, Rolling Stone, Some Girls, Mott The Hopple and the Young Dudes, tr8353 (Box 9)
  - Aircheck Log, tr8354 (Box 9)
  - Allman Brothers I, tr8355 (Box 9)
  - Rocking American Top 30, Scott Shannon, Sounds Like, Badly Butked Near End., tr8356 (Box 9)
  - The Scott Ross Show, tr8357 (Box 9)
  - Love Me Or Leave Me, High Fidelity, M. Hanson, John Brown, tr8358 (Box 9)
  - Karla Bonoff, Interview, M. Grant, tr8359 (Box 9)
  - King Biscuit Flower Hour, Best of Biscuit, Hall & Oates Live, Part 2, tr8360 (Box 9)
  - Alice Cooper, Rick Wakeman, Mike Olfield, Tape 7, Side 1, tr8361 (Box 9)
  - Doug Eupf, Fred Landril, Harry Gordon Live, Fall, 1970; tr8362 (Box 9)
  - John Ettinger, Jamie Thomas/Ithaca High School LAX, Interview, Sports Weekend Roundup, 6/4/1987; tr8363 (Box 9)
  - Music For Lovers Only, Music To Make You Misty, Jackie Gleason Conducts His Orchestra, 9/18/1955; tr8364 (Box 9)
  - Splice, Splice, tr8365 (Box 9)
  - It’s Grand, Editing Exercise, tr8366 (Box 9)
  - Jazz Bed, Them Bulked, PSA Statue, tr8367 (Box 9)
  - Beatles, Blackbeard, Motown, tr8368 (Box 9)
  - VBR, Early Aircheck, tr8369 (Box 9)
  - WVBR Banquet, 1986; tr8370 (Box 9)
  - WVBR, tr8371 (Box 9)
  - Straight Talk, WSEX, Pat Moynihan For Mario Cuomo, tr8372 (Box 9)
  - Bulked, tr8373 (Box 9)
  - Garish Spots, Christmas, tr8374 (Box 9)
  - IF Auction Promo, 2/12/1984; tr8375 (Box 9)
  - "Our Town" Ithaca Festival, 5/25/1983; tr8376 (Box 9)
  - Late 60’s, Pre-oldies, WCBS FM, Jingle Package, tr8377 (Box 9)
  - Promo Brainstorming, Late One Saturday Night, Steven R, Leslie?, Jake, Bruce?, Doug Erpf, tr8378 (Box 9)
  - Side A, News Aircheck, Bridget?, Side B, Movies in Ithaca, This Sunday?, Tracy Richardson, Rainbow Reel, tr8379 (Box 9)
  - John E. Sports, Jess News, Echo Games on Telrec, Xmas Eve, TP, John E., 1985; tr8380 (Box 9)
  - Radio Peking? Hanoi? March 1970, Classic!, March, 1970; tr8381 (Box 9)
  - Glick & Hill, tr8382 (Box 9)
  - Cornell Book Store, Dave Sneide, 11/25/1986; tr8383 (Box 9)
  - FM 93, Hear the Difference, News, Andy Gersh, 1966; tr8384 (Box 9)
  - Schools Out For Summer, tr8385 (Box 9)
  - Collection of Bloopers Paper, 2 pages, tr8386 (Box 9)
  - Part 2, tr8387 (Box 9)
  - Anti-Smoking Promos from Radio Cortland Inc., tr8388 (Box 9)
  - DW/SU Discard Tape (Shreds), Studio B Jam?, tr8389 (Box 9)
  - Unidentified, tr8390 (Box 9)
  - Unidentified, tr8391 (Box 9)
  - No Information, Magnetic Audio Tape, tr8392 (Box 10)
  - American Band Stand 30th, VHS, 10/30/1981; tr8393 (Box 10)
  - Field Day, VHS, 1991; tr8394 (Box 10)
  - Numbers - The Woodshed, VHS, 2/10/1990; tr8395 (Box 10)
  - Democratic Convention, Clinton Acceptance Speech, CNN That Day, VHS, 1992; tr8396 (Box 10)
  - ABBY, tr8397 (Box 10)
  - Gods Must Be Crazy, Cinemax, VHS, 3/30/1986; tr8398 (Box 10)
  - Ithaca Festival, Belly Dance Show, VHS, 1988; tr8399 (Box 10)
  - Rod Stewart Live, VHS, 1981; tr8400 (Box 10)
  - Frank Sinatra #1, Magnetic Tape, tr8401 (Box 10)
  - Frank Sinatra #3, Magnetic Tape, tr8402 (Box 10)
  - Frank Sinatra #4, Magnetic Tape, tr8403 (Box 10)
  - Frank Sinatra #5, Magnetic Tape, tr8404 (Box 10)
  - Frank Sinatra #6, Magnetic Tape, tr8405 (Box 10)
  - Part #1 and 2, 215, Beta 6", tr8406 (Box 10)
  - Part #3, 216, Beta 6", tr8407 (Box 10)
  - Annie Hall, part 1, Beta 6", tr8408 (Box 10)
  - Annie Hall, part 2, Beta 6", tr8409 (Box 10)
  - American Graffiti, Part 1, Beta 6", tr8410 (Box 10)
  - American Graffiti, Part 2, Klute Pt. 1, Beta 6", tr8411 (Box 10)
  - K.H. Show, Beta 6", tr8412 (Box 10)
  - MASH, Part I, Beta 6", tr8413 (Box 10)
  - MASH, Part II, Beta 6", tr8414 (Box 10)
  - Klute III, Tonight 15th pt. 1, Beta 6", tr8415 (Box 10)
  - Tonight Show, 15th, Beta 6", tr8416 (Box 10)
  - What’s Up, Tiger Lilly, Beta 6", tr8417 (Box 10)
  - Saturday Night Live, Turkey, Beta 6", tr8418 (Box 10)
  - Saturday Night Live, Art Garfunkel, Beta 6", tr8419 (Box 10)
  - FREE TAPE, Beta 6", tr8420 (Box 10)
  - Outrageous II, Beta 6", tr8421 (Box 10)
  - Raiders of the Lost Ark, Beta 6", tr8422 (Box 10)
  - Illegible (horse...?), Beta 6", tr8423 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Beta 6", tr8424 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified Beta 6", tr8425 (Box 10)
  - KITT/WOWE/Promo 5, VHS, tr8426 (Box 10)
  - Tay Duky, 9,10,11,12, VHS, tr8427 (Box 10)
  - Thomas Walsh, Storyteller, VHS, 1987; tr8428 (Box 10)
  - SurfDream Hookipa, VHS, tr8429 (Box 10)
  - Tod-E Productions, tr8430 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified VHS, tr8431 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified VHS, tr8432 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified VHS, tr8433 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified VHS, tr8434 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified VHS, tr8435 (Box 10)
  - FMI, Antiwar, 10/7/1967; tr8436 (Box 11)
  - Bee Gees, Gary Kaye, tr8437 (Box 11)
  - Bound For Glory, Bolivian Travel, Caribbean Music, 1968; tr8438 (Box 11)
  - Radio Nederland, Radio Cairo, HCJB, June, 1967; tr8439 (Box 11)
  - VBR, Folk, April, 1973; tr8440 (Box 11)
  - VBR Contest Phoner, April, 1984; tr8441 (Box 11)
  - CG CHR Onite, 1985; tr8442 (Box 11)
  - Weekend Folk/Blues Chad Mitchell, tr8443 (Box 11)
  - Santana I, TAD, tr8444 (Box 11)
  - WRCR, SGA Constitution, 2/9/1968; tr8445 (Box 11)
  - Side 1, Pink Floyd, Genesis, Triumvirat, Side 2, Triumvirat, Joe Walsh, tr8446 (Box 11)
  - Tom Jans at Unicorn, Tom Rush Part 1, 12/5/1975; tr8447 (Box 11)
  - Tom Rush at Unicorn, Second Part, 12/5/1975; tr8448 (Box 11)
  - Jans, Stero Mixdown, tr8449 (Box 11)
  - Montclair High School, Christmas Concert, Side 1, 12/19/1968; tr8450 (Box 11)
  - Montclair High School, Christmas Concert, Side 2, 12/19/1968; tr8451 (Box 11)
  - Montclair High School, Winter Concert, A, 3/15/1968; tr8452 (Box 11)